All The Lord of the Rings related content other than content from the New Line trilogy of The Lord of the Rings films © 2004-2009 The Saul Zaentz Company d/b/a Tolkien Enterprises (“SZC”).  All Rights Reserved.  The Watcher logo, “The Lord of the Rings” and the names of the characters, items, events and places therein are trademarks of SZC under license to Electronic Arts Inc. All content from the Lord of the Rings film trilogy © MMV-MMVII New Line Productions, Inc.  All Rights Reserved. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.